<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Hybrid Cloud Patterns test</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Hybrid Cloud Patterns test</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multi-cluster GitOps with Provisioning</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-10-12-acm-provisioning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-10-12-acm-provisioning/</guid><description>Multi-cluster GitOps with Provisioning Introduction Validated Patterns are an opinionated GitOps environment that lowers the bar for those creating repeatable and declarative deployments.</description></item><item><title>Using subdomain in your OpenShift route definitions</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-09-02-route/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-09-02-route/</guid><description>What Is a route in OpenShift? When creating Community or Validated Patterns using the Validated Patterns framework we often include application workloads, such as a UI, that will need to be accessed externally.</description></item><item><title>Using clusterGroups in the Validated Patterns Framework</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-08-24-clustergroups/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-08-24-clustergroups/</guid><description>What Is a clusterGroup? The Validated Patterns framework defines itself in terms of clusterGroups. A clusterGroup is a set of one or more Kubernetes clusters that are managed to have the same deployments (that is, subscriptions and applications, namespaces and projects) applied to each member of the same clustergroup.</description></item><item><title>Push or Pull?</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-07-15-push-vs-pull/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-07-15-push-vs-pull/</guid><description>Push or Pull? Strategies for Large Scale Technology Change Management on the Edge What is Technology Change Management? There is a segment of the technology industry dedicated to keeping track of what is changing in an IT environment, when and how.</description></item><item><title>Ansible Edge GitOps</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-06-30-ansible-edge-gitops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-06-30-ansible-edge-gitops/</guid><description>Validated Pattern: Ansible Edge GitOps Ansible Edge GitOps: The Why and What As we have been working on new validated patterns and the pattern framework, we have seen a need and interest from the community in expanding the use cases covered by the framework to include other parts of the portfolio besides OpenShift.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Cloud GitOps</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-03-30-multicloud-gitops/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-03-30-multicloud-gitops/</guid><description>Validated Pattern: Multi-Cloud GitOps Hybrid Cloud Patterns: The Story so far Our first foray into the realm of Hybrid Cloud Patterns was the adaptation of the MANUela application and its associated tooling to ArgoCD and Tekton, to demonstrate the deployment of a fairly involved IoT application designed to monitor industrial equipment and use AI/ML techniques to predict failure.</description></item><item><title>To musthave or to mustonlyhave</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-03-23-acm-mustonlyhave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2022-03-23-acm-mustonlyhave/</guid><description>Recently a user reported an issue when using the multicloud-gitops pattern: Namely, after testing changes in a feature branch (adding a helm application), said changes were not appearing on the remote clusters.</description></item><item><title>Medical Diagnosis</title><link>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2021-12-31-medical-diagnosis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.acksyn.org/blog/2021-12-31-medical-diagnosis/</guid><description>Validated Pattern: Medical Diagnosis Our team recently completed the development of a validated pattern that showcases the capabilities we have at our fingertips when we combine OpenShift and other cutting edge Red Hat technologies to deliver a solution.</description></item></channel></rss>